cipinet.com 2013-09-05

# Cipinet Privacy Policy

Cipinet takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**Privacy Policy Overview**

This Privacy Policy covers how Cipinet treats personal information Cipinet collects and records when you submit your website for inclusion in Cipinet Web Directory. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies or individuals that Cipinet campaigns for, listed on Cipinet web directory. This policy also does not apply to people Cipinet does not employ or manage. Please verify their Privacy Policy by visiting their website.

**Information Collection and Use**

For web site submission, visitors must create an account with us. Account activation code is emailed to verify email address. We ask for website and some personal information. Every information submitted is saved for future reference. Email address is only used for sending email when your website is either approved, disapproved or there is a need to contact member. Basic, Regular, Premium Permanent or Sponsored link submission is required to get listed. Only non-commercial free information sites and quality websites are accepted in Basic listing. Listing will be listed higher in selected subcategory and directory search result pages based on link type. At the time of review, if the web site is not found suitable, it will not be approved and total amount paid will be refunded. No money will be refunded at any time if the website is approved. Website will be disapproved if Terms and Conditions and submission guidelines are not followed or an editor does not find it suitable for inclusion. Discounted offer, if any, is valid from the day it appears on Login Page and is valid till the date mentioned.

**Refund Policy**

If paid web page submission is not found suitable, total amount paid will be refunded. No money will be refunded at any time if the website is approved. Website will be disapproved if Terms and Conditions and submission guidelines are not followed or an editor does not find it suitable for inclusion. For more information about pricing, please visit [submission detail page](http://www.cipinet.com/submit.php). 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Cipinet does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people and/or affiliated and non-affiliated companies.

**Cookies**

Cookies are used on our website for the purpose of logging into your account.

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on Cipinet websites displaying AdSense for ads. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Newsletters**

Guests who create a membership account to submit a web site for inclusion in Cipinet Web Directory will not be entitled to receive a newsletter. Only those who opt to Join our Newsletter by filling the Newsletter form will receive the newsletter. Newsletter will be sent at the most twice a month and will have important news related to Search Engine Marketing, Web Services and Cipinet offers if any. You can anytime unsubscribe from receiving the newsletter.

**Security**

Cipinet stores your personal information inside our premises under safe custody. Access is limited to those employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Cipinet may amend or update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our Home Page and Privacy Policy page.

Last Updated on June 06, 2013
